大家过来集合一下
Okay, everybody, gather 'round.
原来今天是"带女朋友来上班日"啊
Who knew it was "Bring your girlfriend to work" day?
她不是我女朋友
She is not my girlfriend.
朱蒂是心肺复苏人偶
Judy is a CPR doll,
也是这餐厅里 工作最努力的女孩
and the hardest-working girl in this diner.
阿憨 你不该把性爱人偶带来公共场合哦
Oh, Han, you shouldn't bring your sex doll out in public.
这不是我的女友或我的性爱人偶
This is not my girlfriend or a sex doll!
厄尔 过来一下
Earl, come over.
我们要用朱蒂来练习怎么心肺复苏
We're going to use Judy to learn how to resuscitate.
我签过"拒绝心肺复苏术"
I have a "Do not resuscitate" clause,
就是"拒绝帮人心肺复苏"的意思
as in, I do not resuscitate others.
奥列格
Oleg.
阿憨 叫我干嘛
What's up, Han?
朱蒂 你来啦
Oh, hey, Judy.
你怎么会认识朱蒂
How do you know Judy?
如此丰满的上身 她绝对声名远播啊
With a torso like that, she gets around.
好了 我来示范
Okay, I will demonstrate.
惨了
Oh, no!
朱蒂被东西噎到了
Judy's choking on something!
我们知道不是被你的"小鸡"噎到
Well, we know it's not you.
首先我们先把她的头往后倾
First you have to tilt the head back
保持呼吸道畅通后 吹气
and clear the airway and blow.
麦克斯 我们在见证他的初吻
Oh, Max, I think we're witnessing his first kiss.
是第四次好吗 谢谢
Fourth, thank you very much.
阿憨 你浪费时间搞前戏亲她干嘛
Han, why are you wasting your time kissing her?
她又没手反抗
She doesn't have any arms.
直接开干啊
Just go for it.
大家好啊 今天可是大日子呢
What's up, everybody? Big day today.
虽然不及耶稣诞辰 但也是某个
Not as big as Christmas, but still marks the arrival
天之骄女的诞生日哦 我的
of someone very blessed: me.
我们都知道
Yeah, we get it.
你提起你生日的次数简直比
You talk about your birthday more than
侃爷提起自己的次数还多
Kanye West talks about Kanye West.
卡洛琳 我还以为你又会哭呢
Caroline, I thought you would be crying.
你生日时哭一顿 就跟前迪士尼明星
Tears on your birthday have become as expected
沦落到进勒戒所一样稀松平常
as an ex-Disney star going to rehab.
我干嘛要哭
Why would I be sad?
我健健康康 生意也渐渐在萌芽
I have my health, a business that's budding--
胸部还是一潭死水
Boobs that aren't.
我不吃生日这套
I don't believe in birthdays.
你心里感觉的才是真的年纪
You're only as old as you feel.
所以我有"心如死灰"那么多岁了
Which makes me nothing years old.
说到灰尘般大
Speaking of nothing...
卡洛琳 今晚还去披萨店庆生吗
Caroline, are we still on for Two Boots pizza tonight?
今天餐厅会提早关来庆祝你的诞辰
I'm closing the diner early in honor of your birthday,
绝对不只是因为市政府要求
and just not because the city has demanded to
处理餐厅黑霉菌的问题
look into the black mold situation.
当然啦 阿憨
Absolutely, Han.
你可以选择一片披萨两种料
You can have one slice with two toppings
或两片披萨一种料
or two slices with one topping,
而我的生日蛋糕是免费的水果馅饼
and my birthday cake is a free flan
是我跟洗碗工调情换来的
'cause I flirted with the dishwasher.
卡洛琳 亲 如果我是你
Caroline, sweetheart, if I was you,
我现在就找块玻璃窗 一头撞死自己算了
I would just put my head through a plate glass window.
好了 各位
Okay, everybody.
我有两件事请要宣布 都是好消息
I have two announcements, both good news.
第一件事 在三明治里发现有鸟嘴的男的
First, the guy who found the beak in his sandwich
决定不提告了
is not suing,
第二 我要干那件事 问那个"问题"了
and second, I'm gonna pop the question to Sophie.
毕竟其他能"干"的你全干过了
Well, you've already popped everything else.
你们觉得呢
What do you think?
大家都说"钻石是女人最好的朋友"
They say diamonds are a girl's best friend.
真的吗
Oh, really?
我还以为女人最好的朋友
I thought a girl's best friend
是比自己胖一点的朋友呢
was someone just a little fatter than her.
这是我在俄国的奶奶传下来的
It was my grandma's from Russia.
我让我亲戚吞下肚子里 带来美国
I had my cousin Svela swallow it to bring it to America.
她成功出了海关 戒指也成功出了她肛门
She passed customs, then she passed this.
经过五六回的冲洗
Five, six rinses later, boom!
免屎又免税
Duty free.
好吧 好歹比在凯式珠宝买来得好
Well, I guess that's better than getting it at Kay.
苏菲知道你要求婚吗
Is Sophie expecting it?
当然啦
Of course.
她不喜欢惊喜
She doesn't like surprises
因为她家的谷仓当年就是被
since her family barn was torched
精神状况不稳定的帮工给突然放火烧掉
by a mentally unstable farmhand.
我有一件物品要请卡洛琳·钱宁签收
Hi, I have a delivery for Caroline Channing
来自马丁·钱宁先生
from Martin Channing.
我是老爸从监狱寄来的生日礼物
Oh, it's a birthday gift from my daddy all the way from prison.
去年他亲手做了手工通心粉相框给我
Last year, he made me a macaroni art picture frame.
想当年 他可曾为替朋友办单身派对
I mean, the man once rented Miami
把整个迈阿密[音似通心粉]租下来呢
for a friend's bachelor party.
那相框好歹让我们饱餐两天
Hey, that picture frame fed us for two days.
这东西不是意大利面
Yeah, well, this thing is not pasta,
而且大到过不了这个门
and it's too big to fit through the door.
我三个月前也是这样
And so was I three months ago.
是真的
No, really.
我以前坐飞机 座位显示是"第三排"
My seat on an airplane used to be Row Three.
瞧 就在街上
There it is in the street.
塞满汉堡肉的保险套吗
A condom full of hamburger meat?
天啊
Oh, my God.
那是兰博基尼吗
Is that a Lamborghini?
等等
Wait.
那是我的兰博基尼吗
Is that my Lamborghini?
是的 是兰博基尼公牛双门超跑
Yeah, it's a Lamborghini Aventador Roadster.
监狱里的艺术工艺品越来越精致了啊
Prison arts and crafts has gotten pretty fancy.
这车客制化制造需要四年左右
Well, it takes four years for these cars to be custom-made.
这台是2011年订购的
This one was ordered in 2011.
是的 我爸当时帮我订的
That's right, my father ordered this for me
那时候他还有钱
when he still had money.
改正一下 当时他还有别人的钱
Correction: When he had everyone else's money.
我爸唯一给我的就是条怪怪的染色体
All my father ever gave me was that one iffy chromosome.
去吧
Well, here you go.
它是你的了
It's all yours.
我要走回家了
I'm gonna walk home.
减肥靠的就是健康的选择
It's all about healthy choices.
我有车了
I got a car!
我们有车了
We got a car!
靠 有人把蝙蝠战车漆成白色的了
Damn, someone painted the Batmobile white.
就不能有黑色的帅气东西吗
Can't we have anything?
这是台售价45万美元的跑车
That's a $450,000 sports car.
是啊
I know.
再加上可堆叠式洗衣/烘干机与一台房车
Add a stackable washer/dryer and a motor home,
感觉卡洛琳就像赢了综艺节目大奖呢
and it's like Caroline won the Showcase Showdown.
从0加速到100只需2.9秒
It goes from 0 to 100 in 2.9 seconds.
说到秒
And speaking of seconds,
披萨店我要多叫一份[秒]
I'm getting seconds at Two Boots,
让那个有钱的婊子付
and that rich bitch is paying.
不许靠近 《东京漂移》
Back off, Tokyo Drift.
这是我们的逃命车
This is our getaway car.
意思就是离我们车远点[逃命]
And by that, I mean get away from it.
车子这种东西 第一次开出去
You know, a car like this depreciates 50%
就会直接贬值一半
the minute you drive it off the lot.
所以我都开我的丰田雅力士
That's why I drive my Toyota Yaris.
吹牛老爹来了吗[饶舌歌手]
Is P. Diddy here?
等等 还是特德·特纳[亿万富翁]呢
Wait a minute. Is it Ted Turner?
不是什么牛逼人的车
No one cool owns it.
是卡洛琳的
It's Caroline's.
如果有这种车
Now, this is the kind of car
要我做什么我都会统统答应
that I would say yes to anything in.
除了去看音乐剧《更年期》之外的所有事
Anything except tickets to Menopause The Musical.
卡洛琳 好赞的车啊
Oh, hey, Caroline. Nice car.
我一直都喜欢你多过麦克斯
I always liked you more than Max.
你知道的吧 好姐妹
You know that, right, girl?
是吗
Really?
因为昨天 我听到你大声问麦克斯
'Cause yesterday, I heard you yell to Max,
"卡洛琳是要47还是48岁了
"Is Caroline turning 47 or 48?
她这人感觉好像65岁了啊"
'Cause she acts like she's 65."
是啊
Yeah.
我得知道你的生日卡上要写什么嘛
Yeah, I wanted to know what to write in your birthday card.
大家都离这台车远点
Well, everyone away from the car.
我刚跟我爸通完电话
I just got off the phone with my dad.
这台车明早就会被查封
The car is being seized in the morning.
他们不会让我留下这份礼物
Turns out they won't let me keep my present.
感觉就像我八岁生日时
It's just like my eighth birthday
让我把送我的麦考利·克金还回去一样
when they made me return Macaulay Culkin.
你家人送你个小男孩啊
They bought you a boy?
真是有钱到没边
You were rich.
车就在面前 却用都不能用
Oh, boy, the car's right here, and you can't even use it.
就像有你俩服务员一样 屁用没有
That's like me having you two for waitresses.
卡洛琳 我能请你帮个忙吗
Caroline, can I ask you a favor?
别想用我的车给苏菲求婚
You're not using the car to propose to Sophie.
你也听到她多喜欢那台车了
You heard how much she liked it.
而且也比我的原计划有档次
And it's a little bit classier than my original plan:
在纽约郊区吃晚餐 看斗鸡
dinner and a cock fight in Yonkers.
我没在偷听啊
Not that I'm listening,
但我绝对不要在基佬吧里被人求婚
but I'm not gonna get proposed to at a gay bar.
这下好了 基酒吧的计划也泡汤了
Great, now my gay bar idea is out also.
奥列格 不行
No, Oleg.
我把车还回去时 车上不能有刮痕 凹洞
I can't return the car with scratches, dents,
或者性病
or chlamydia.
但我们还是能开一下吧
But we can still drive it, right?
我都涂了一个月的药了 应该治好了
I mean, I've been on that cream for like a month.
麦克斯 兰博基尼俱乐部第九规矩是什么
Max, what is the ninth rule of the Lamborghini Club?
车上不许喝酒
No red drinks in the car.
但我的第一号规矩是
Here's my number one rule:
如果你想让我睡在里面
If you're going to make me sleep in it,
你就得让我在里面喝
I am going to drink in it.
你小心点
Well, just be careful.
我只剩最后一张消毒湿纸巾了
I only have one Clorox wipe
这张得撑到明年生日呢
that has to last till my next birthday,
而且因为放太久 湿巾都干了大半了
and it's already lost a lot of its moisture.
我们为什么要呆坐在这里呢
I don't see why we have to just sit here.
我们不能开这车
We can't drive it.
我爸说 万一这车子出事了
My dad said if anything happens to it,
我们就得负责
we'll be responsible.
哪能出什么事啊
What could possibly happen
就去墨西哥边境城市进点大麻回来而已
on a weed run to deep Tijuana?
我真希望没收到过这台车
You know, I wish this car never came,
也从没坐到这台车上过
and I wish I never sat in it.
就跟我现在不去百货公司一样
It's the same reason I don't go to Barneys.
我不想要靠近我买不起的事物
I don't like to be around things I can't afford anymore.
我也是因为这样才不去一元店的
Same reason I don't go to the 99 Cent Store.
里面有一套玩具网球组
There's a Nerf tennis set
一半在地上 一半在垃圾桶里
half on the floor, half in the bin,
但是我还是只能空手而归
none of it going home with me.
我本来还试着用正面态度面对我今年生日
I was trying to be positive about my birthday this year,
但麦克斯 如果我爸爸没出事
but, Max, if things hadn't happened with my father,
今晚或许我真能过个魔力的生日
tonight would have been a magical birthday for me.
我也展现点魔力给你瞧瞧
Hey, there was some magic.
我把五杯伏特加混雪碧弄消失了
I personally made five vodka Sprites disappear.
厉害吧
Ta-da!
我会坐上车 开到汉普顿[度假胜地]
I would've got in the car and driven out to the Hamptons,
我们可以整晚坐在海滩边
and we'd sit on the beach all night
让当地人抓龙虾给我们吃
having lobster caught by one of the townies
再一边喝红酒 一边拍个鸭嘴自拍
and drink champagne while taking duckface selfies
直到日出
till the sun came up.
在你整段剧情里 我是那个"当地人"
FYI, I'm the townie in this scenario,
我恨你们全部人
and I hate all of you.
但我不是在做那些事 而是在过最烂的生日
Instead of doing any of that, I'm having the worst birthday.
这感觉大概比黛米·摩尔
I probably feel worse than Demi Moore did
过50岁生日时还糟吧
when she turned 50.
你就乖乖睡吧
Yes, just go to sleep.
你明天醒了以后会开心点的
You'll feel better tomorrow when you wake up.
前提是那个手里拿着弹簧刀
I mean, if that guy with the switchblade
说了会回来报仇的男人没有回来
doesn't come back like he promised he would.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
卡洛琳 醒醒
Caroline, wake up.
我们到海滩了
We're at the beach.
我开车把我们载到汉普顿啦
I drove us out to the Hamptons.
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
我们到汉普顿了
We're in the Hamptons?
我们居然到汉普顿了
我们怎么会来到汉普顿
How are we in the Hamptons?
我到底睡了多久啊
How long have I been sleeping?
三个小时左右吧
Three hours, give or take.
你还放了两个屁
You farted twice.
我怎么就没醒呢
How did I not wake up?
就是啊 味道超难闻
I know. It was pretty bad.
第二个屁让我误以为开车经过了臭鸡蛋镇呢
After that last one, I thought we were going through Egg Town.
麦克斯 你又来了
Max, you did it again.
你对我下药了 是吗
You roofied me, didn't you?
那是必须的呀
Of course I did.
你一边哭哭哭 一边叨叨叨汉普顿
You were crying and babbling about the Hamptons,
所以我必须把你迷晕呀
so I had to put you down.
你答应过我不会再做这种事
You promised you wouldn't again.
上次你害我昏睡了整整两天
The last time, I was out for two days.
那是因为我真的很想好好看完《权利的游戏》
Yeah, I really just needed to get through Game of Thrones
而不是听某人在主角乱伦的时候讲道理
without someone talking during the incest.
你到底有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?
你有纸和笔可以记下来吗
Have you got a pen and paper?
你明知道我不想这么做
You knew I didn't want to do this.
你什么也不想做 所以我帮你做了
You never want to do anything, so I did it for you.
这辆车价值45万美元
You took a $450,000 car,
我们本来连碰都不该碰
a car we're not even supposed to be touching,
而你却开着它一路兜风来汉普顿
on a joyride to the Hamptons?
是你想来这里
You wanted to be here.
现在你来了
You are here.
好好享受吧
Just enjoy it.
我没心情享受
I can't enjoy it.
斯科蒂 到舰桥来
Scotty to the bridge.
我是柯克舰长
This is Captain Kirk.
斯科蒂 到舰桥来
Scotty to the bridge.
你开车碾过沙丘 然后开到沙滩上来吗
You drove over the dunes and onto the beach?
我不是故意的
Not intentionally.
我本来想停下 但这辆车当时说
I tried to stop it, but this car was like,
"姑娘 不许停"
"Mm, no, girl."
我的老天
Oh, my God.
那车身上有没有划痕
Did it get any scratches?
麦克斯 快下车 帮我看看有没有划痕
Max, get out of the car, and help me look for scratches.
亏你还说你在汉普顿会变得更有趣
You said you were more fun in the Hamptons.
都是假的
Not true.
苏鲁先生 发射所有光炮[星际迷航]
Mr. Sulu, fire all phasers.
没有划痕 兰博基尼完好无损
No scratches. The Lamborghini is fine.
但多亏了你 现在我成了美而廉租车公司了
But thanks to you, I'm a Rent-A-Wreck.
走吧 我们得把车弄回去
Come on, we have to get this car back.
会弄回去的 你放心吧
We will. Jeez, relax.
我们还有时间
We still have time.
听着 你说你想来这里
Look, you said you wanted to be here.
现在你来了 而且我们不会轻易离开
You're here, and we are not leaving
除非你做一些在海滩上会做的事
till you do something beach-y,
比如走到海里
like walk in the water
或发现《大白鲨》里被吃了一半的女尸
or find a half-eaten lady from Jaws.
不 不行 还是走吧
No. No way. Let's go.
快把你的鞋子脱下
Just take off your shoes or something.
不要
No.
快脱下鞋子 感受下沙子
Just take off your shoes and feel the sand.
麦克斯 麦克斯 住手
Max! Max, stop.
自从贾斯汀·汀布莱克
I haven't had a proper pedicure
上次发布单曲后 我就没做过美足护理了
since Justin Timberlake released a single.
快 动动你的脚
There. Now move your foot around.
不要
No.
不 不 不
No. No! No.
哇哦 感觉真好
Oh, yeah. That feels nice.
冰凉的沙子在我的脚趾间
The cold sand between my toes.
但麦克斯 不许看
But, Max, don't look.
中间那个脚趾很恐怖
That middle nail's a horror show.
晚了
Too late.
我刚有一瞬间以为是裂开的开心果呢
I thought it was a pistachio for a second.
麦克斯 你有多喜欢海滩呀
Max, how much do you love the beach?
不知道 我从来没去过
I don't know. I've never been to one.
你从来没来过海滩
You've never been to a beach?
没 来干嘛啊
No. What's the point?
我又没有挖宝金属探测器
I don't own a metal detector.
好啦 时间到
Well, time's up.
但我们才刚坐下
But we just sat down.
我知道 但如果我们现在走
I know, but if we leave right now,
就还有时间从麦当劳的
we'll still have enough time to
得来速车道呼啸而过
blow through a McDonald's drive-through
就像《回到未来》里的一样
like something from Back to the Future.
好吧 我打算在沙子上写下咱俩的名字
Well, I'm gonna write our names in the sand
因为我很喜欢你今天做的事
'cause it was a really nice thing
对我下药 绑架我
for you to drug me, kidnap me,
偷了我的车 把我带来这
and steal my car to get me out here.
别客气 朋友嘛
Hey, we're friends.
好啦 我先把这车掉个头
All right, I'll just turn this baby around.
糟糕
Uh-oh.
"糟糕"什么
What's "Uh-oh"?
什么"糟糕"了
What is "Uh-oh"?
车子陷进沙子里出不来了吗
Are we stuck in the sand?
你完全正确地解读了"糟糕"的意思
You have correctly identified the meaning of "Uh-oh."
我真喜欢我们无需完整的句子
I love that we don't need full sentences
就能相互交流的感觉
to communicate anymore.
再试
Try it again.
还是不行
Nope.
跟运动员"狂欢"后 回家都没这么"辛苦"
I've had less trouble getting out of athlete's apartments.
你给我下去推车
Well, you're gonna have to get out and push.
为什么非得让我推
Why do I have to push?
谁让你对我下药 绑架我
Because you're the one who drugged me, kidnapped me,
还偷了我的车
and stole my car.
是是是
Exactly.
大部分活儿都被我承包了
I've already done the lion's share of the work.
而且这是我们的车
And it's our car.
好吧 去就去
Fine, I'll do it.
门开了 乌乎拉中尉[星际迷航]
Door's up, Lieutenant Uhura.
现在这情况一点都不好笑好吗
It stopped being funny when we got stuck.
老天 别担心嘛
God, don't worry.
我曾用自己的双手把一个272公斤的女人
I got a 600-pound woman out of a booth
从卡座里拽出来 我没在怕的
at the diner with my bare hands. I'm fearless.
挂空挡 像我当时对那女的做的一样
Toss her in neutral like I did with that lady.
沙子和高跟鞋 这组合太销魂了
Sand and heels. Not a good combo.
销魂 销魂 超级销魂
Not a good combo. Not a good combo.
好了
Oh, all right.
All right.
我要加速了
I'm gonna floor it.
从一数到三
On the count of three.
一 二
One, two...
"我太兴奋 过早了"
I got excited. I went early.
如果每次听到这句话都存一毛钱
If I had a dime for every time I heard that,
老娘都可以买下这辆车了
I could buy this car.
好啦 再试一遍
All right, let's try again.
一 二
One, two...
妈的 这次是故意的吧
Okay, that was on purpose.
有那么一点儿吧
A little bit.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我真不敢相信我不敢相信此情此景
I can't believe that I can't believe it,
但我真的不敢相信
but I really can't believe it.
我们闯大祸了
We are in very big trouble,
而且还不是身处汉普顿好的那一边
and we're not even in the good Hamptons.
我只不过是想做件好事而已
I was trying to do something nice.
第一次 也是最后一次
First time, last time.
你知道你是什么吗
You know what you are?
你是鲁莽女
You are reckless.
一直以来
You know, all this time,
我以为你是一个要么冲要么死的女汉子
I thought you were a ride-or-die kind of bitch.
我就是一个要么冲要么死的女汉子
I am a ride-or-die kind of bitch.
什么是"要么冲要么死的女汉子"
What's a ride-or-die kind of bitch?
你是要上网搜吗
Are you Googling "Ride-or-die kind of bitch"?
我也想 但我手机信号不好
I would be, but I only have two bars.
听着 我们有两个选择
Look, we have two options:
要么把车开出沙滩 要么让海浪把我们带走
Get the car out of the sand, or let the tide take us.
海浪带走这主意可以考虑
Put a pin in that tide thing,
这主意听起来不错
'cause I like the sound of it.
我们把车开回市里的时间都很紧绷了
We barely have enough time to get this car back to the city,
开不回去就要还45万
or we owe $450,000.
而我只有3美元 而且其中2美元还是硬币
And I only have $3, and 2 of it's in nickels.
现在快上车
Now get in the car.
你居然藏有硬币
You're hoarding nickels,
而我去一元店却因为没钱空手而归
and I'm walking out of the 99 Cent Store empty-handed?
现在老娘气大了
Now I'm mad.
准备
Get ready.
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?
我要把车推出去
I'm pushing us out of here.
因为我是一个要么冲要么死的女汉子
Because I'm a ride-or-die kind of bitch!
应该是吧
I think.
现在快踩油门
Now hit it!
你做了什么 用屁把我们嘣出来了吗
What'd you do? Fart us out of the ditch?
说真的 卡洛琳 踩油门啊
Seriously, Caroline, step on it.
不行 麦克斯
No, Max.
我们不能冒着出车祸的危险开快车
We can't risk getting into an accident.
万一没死怎么办
What if it's not fatal?
慢慢开兰博基尼就像去连锁海鲜餐厅
Driving a Lamborghini slow is like going to Red Lobster
却没有点他们的招牌菜切达湾软饼
and not getting the Cheddar Bay biscuits.
拜托 趁现在能还开我们就尽情享受嘛
Come on, we got to enjoy this car while we can.
-踩油门 -好啦
- Hit the gas. - All right.
我就踩到我能接受约会对象年龄的最大值
I'll take it up to the top of my age dating window.
那我来踩到我的最大值
And I'll take it to the top of mine.
放手 好好玩嘛
Let go. Have some fun.
不 别压我的脚
No, don't push on my leg!
别压我的脚
Don't push on my--
太棒了
Yes! Yes!
史上最棒的生日
Best birthday ever!
我们要学《末路狂花》那样吗
Should we Thelma and Louise it?
你是说飞越悬崖吗
You mean drive over a cliff?
不 我是说戴上墨镜手拉手
No, I mean wear sunglasses and hold hands.
她们飞越了悬崖吗
They drive over a cliff?
我一直没有看完那部电影
I never saw the end.
她们回来了
There they are.
你们俩早上有按时把车还回去吗
Did you girls get the car back in time this morning?
有 时间刚刚好 多亏了卡洛琳
Yep, just in time, thanks to Caroline.
她完全无视限速的标志
She was ignoring speed limit signs
就像她无视流浪汉一样
like she does homeless people.
有个州警用四个字形容我开车
A state trooper called my driving
"刑事过失"
criminally negligent.
我真为你骄傲
I was so proud.
我甚至可能有点过于激动
I might've even gotten emotional,
但我必须巧舌如簧求警察别开罚单
but I had to talk our way out of the ticket,
而且我必须在脱掉衣服时保持专业
and I like to be professional when my shirt's off.
你们没被开罚单吗
You didn't get a ticket?
昨天我就因为走进全食超市而被捕了
Yesterday, I got arrested for just walking into Whole Foods.
真不敢相信我头发里还有沙子
I can't believe I still have sand in my hair.
如果你唯一有沙子的地方是你的头发
If the only place you still have sand is in your hair,
那恭喜你
you're lucky.
沙多到我底下的"蚌"都要生珍珠了
I'm about to make a pearl down there.
哎哟 那不是穷鬼芭比吗
Oh, hey, there, destitute Barbie.
真可惜你的爱车没了
Sorry you lost the dream car.
我去我的卡座啦
Anyway, I'll be in my booth.
苏菲 漂亮的宝贝
Sophie, beautiful baby...
我已经把我的求婚地点缩小到三个范围了
I've narrowed down the site of my proposal to three options:
一 我们初次相遇的地方
A, the place we met...
二 我们最常做爱的地方
B, the place we've had sex most often...
三 我们最近一次做爱的地方
or C, the place we've had sex most recently.
且慢 且慢
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
这三个地方都是这个卡座
All three of those places are this booth!
那就对了
That's right.
苏菲·科臣斯基
Sophie Kachinsky...
他要在咱们的餐厅求婚吗
He's proposing at the diner?
他要怎么求 用洋葱圈当戒指吗
What's he gonna do? Put an onion ring on it?
我爱这戒指
I love that.
我本来打算拒绝你
You know, I was planning on saying no
让你多求我几个小时 但...
and making you beg for a few hours, but...
我太爱你了
I just love you too much.
这画面没有平时那么恶心嘛
Aw, that's so not as gross as normal.
现在有了
Now it is.